Guide to the Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life records, 1964-2012 UA.09.12.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2013-0026, 1964-2011
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Total Membership Education: Something of Value, circa 2000 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Total Membership Education: Sexual Assault Awareness, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Total Membership Education: Alcohol Info, To distribute, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Safety Info: Safety Issues (Off East, etc.), 1998 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Safety Info: Duke Police/Public Information Manager, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Safety Info, To distribute, circa 2000 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Safety Info: Safe Rides Improvement Proposal, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Judicial Board Apps, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Living Groups, 2009 (Box 6)
  - Pan Hellenic Files: RM: Fax Cover Sheets, circa 1990 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Panhellenic Facilities: Facilities Needs (Historical Data), 1994-1998 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Panhellenic Facilities: Building Proposal (1990), 1983-1997 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Panhellenic Facilities: Duke Panhellenic Association Program Statement in Support of a Facilities Request by Duke University Sororities, Unfoldered, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Area Coordinator Manual: George Washington University, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Area Coordinator Manual: Colgate, 2003 January-July (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Area Coordinator Manual: Cornell, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Area Coordinator Manual: Emory, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Area Coordinator Manual: Wake Forest, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Area Coordinator Manual: USC, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Area Coordinator Manual: University of Pennsylvania, 2002-2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: DOS, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Women's Initiative, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Honor Societies, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dan Files: Student Organization Handbook, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Unfoldered, 2003-2006 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Untitled, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Todd Adams, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Unfoldered, 2002-2004 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Untitled, 2004-2005 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Meetings, 1990-1994 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Unfoldered, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Untitled, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Fall Leadership Retreat, FSL Strengths/Weaknesses, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Retreat Todd Adams, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Unfoldered, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: Summer Fraternity and Sorority Life: Staff Retreat, 2001-2002 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Leadership Conferences: FSL Leadership Retreat: Millenium Hotel, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Annual Fund Executive Committee Meeting, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Life: Greek Summit, 2000-2003 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: Unfoldered, 2009 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: Greek Community Standard, 2007 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: Fraternity and Sorority Life Two Year Plan, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: Budget Staff, 2008-2009 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: Alpha Omicron Pi, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: Sue, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: CEC, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled A: Staff Meeting, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Kappa Sigma: Eta Prime Chapter, Duke University, 2008 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Unfoldered, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Unfoldered, 2003-2009 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: DGEL, 2009 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Si Se Puede, Unfoldered, 2010 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Unfoldered, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Kiser-Hill Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Panhellenic Recruitment, 2008-2011 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: Journal of the Indiana Student Personnel Association, 2009 (Box 6)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC Step Show, Homecoming, Fall, 2006 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC Step Show, Greek Week, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: BSAI Step Show, 2006 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHS Homecoming Step Show, Fall, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Homecoming Step Show, Fall, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC BSAI Step Show, Spring, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Homecoming Step Show, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Giles: BSAI Step Show, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Homecoming Step Show, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC Step Show, Spring, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Walter Kimbrough, NPHC Program, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC Week, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Unfoldered, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC Week, Freek Fest et al, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC Calendar Code, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC Intake Requirements, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NBGLC - Todd, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC, Unfoldered, 2001-2003 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: NPHC, 2001-2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Financial Information, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Greek Week, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Unfoldered, 1999-2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Intake, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled B: Committees, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled B: NPHC Constitution, 1999-2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled B: Unfoldered 13, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled B: NPHC, Inc. Constitution and Bylaws, 1993-1999 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled B: Greek Life Forum, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled C: Unfoldered 14, circa 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled C: Step Show, Spring, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled C: Step Show, 2000-2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled C: Step Show, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel files: Untitled C: Step Shows, 2001 (Video-cassette UA09120002-DVCAM-0001, Video-cassette UA090120002-DVCAM-0002)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled D: Step Show, Fall, 2000-2001 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled D: Unfoldered, 2001-2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled D: Untitled, 2000-2001 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled D: NPHC Calendar, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Certificate of Recognition, Todd Adams, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled E: Duke Correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled E: Duke University Chapter of the NPHC Judicial Code, circa 1999 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled E: Duke University Recognition and Guidelines, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled E: Membership Roster, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled E: Correspondence, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled F: Rush, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled F: Retreat Planning, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled F: Responsibilities of Advisor, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled G: National Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled G: National Information, 1999 February-November (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled G: Greek Expansion, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled H: Alpha Pi Alpha, 1995-2001 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled H: Alpha Kappa Alpha, 1992-1993; 1996-2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled I: Delta Sigma Theta, 1993-2001 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled J: Sigma Gamma Rho, 1995-2001 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled J: Zeta Phi Beta, 1993-2001 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled K: Omega Psi Phi, 1993-2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled K: Kappa Alpha Psi, 1992-2002 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled L: Resources, 1999-2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled L: Conferences, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled L: Alcohol, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Unfoldered 15, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Alpha Epsilon Pi, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Alpha Tau Omega, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Beta Theta Pi, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Delta Sigma Phi, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Kappa Alpha Order, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Phi Delta Theta, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Pi Kappa Alpha, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Sigma Chi, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Sigma Nu, 2003-2004 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: GJB Files: Delta Tau Delta, 2003-2004 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled M: Unfoldered 16, 2003-2006 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Annual Review: Untitled 7, 1999-2001 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Greek Life Task Force: Unfoldered 17, 1994-2006 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Greek Life Task Force: Final Report, Task Force on Greek Affairs, 1994 March-April (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Greek Life Task Force: Growth of Selective Living Groups: Task Force, 2001-2003 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: Campus Culture, Spring, 2006-2007 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: Duke Recognition Guidelines (Greek), Historical, 1995-2006 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: Unfoldered 18, 2000-2005 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: North American Interfraternity Conference (NIC) Report to Duke, 1999 February-April (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: North American Interfraternity Conference (NIC) Report to Duke, 1994 August-September (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: Unfoldered 19, 1999-2003 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: Parental Notification and Assessment, 2000 October-December (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: Unfoldered 20, 1998-2000 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled N: Committee Task Force Reports, 2000 March-December (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled O: Unfoldered 21, 2005 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled P: Unfoldered 22, 2002-2005 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled P: FSL Strategic Plan FY 2004-2006, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled P: FSL FY 2003-2004 Goals/Objectives (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled P: FSL Goals/Objectives, 2005 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled P: Unfoldered 23, 2005 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled P: FSL Staff Retreat, 2005 June-August (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled Q: Unfoldered 24, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled Q: Duke SA Strategic Plan, 1998-2000 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled R: Event Planning: Event Advising Center, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled R: Event Oversight Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled R: Fall 2000-Spring 2001 Event Advising Weekend Calendar, 2000-2002 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Unfoldered 25, 2000-2007 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Duke University, Judicial Statistics, 2001-2006 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Unfoldered 26, 2000-2001 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Duke Judicial Procedures, 1997-2000 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Unfoldered 27, 2002 July-September (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: 2000-2001 Statistics (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Judicial Letter Examples, 1999-2001 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Unfoldered 28, 1997-2001 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: West Campus Feedback, Student Life/Alcohol, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled S: Unfoldered 29, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled T: Unfoldered 30, 2001-2004 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled T: Unfoldered 31, 2000-2003 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled T: Duke Alcohol Policy, 1994-1997 (Box 8)
  - Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled T: Untitled, 2001 (Box 8)
  - 006F: Unfoldered 32, 2001-2002 (Box 8)
  - 006F: Untitled U: Example Recruitment Brochures, 2003-2004 (Box 8)
  - 006F: Untitled U: Unfoldered 33, circa 2003 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Untitled U: Untitled 9, 2001-2002 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Untitled U: Unfoldered 34, 2002-2004 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Untitled U: Unfoldered 35, 2002-2007 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Greek Way: Unfoldered 36, 2001-2002 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Greek Way: Unfoldered 37, 1999-2000 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Greek Way: Unfoldered 38, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Greek Way: Unfoldered 39, 1994-1996 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Greek Way: Unfoldered 40, 1988-1993 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Greek Way: Unfoldered 41, 1969-1981 (Box 9)
  - 006F: Fraternity/Sorority Rush: Committees, 1986-1989 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Unfoldered 42, 1997-2003 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Recognition Guidelines Interfraternity Council, 1995-1999 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Alcohol Policy Interfraternity Council, 1997-2000 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Faculty Advisors Interfraternity Council, 1997-2001 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Risk Management Interfraternity Council, 1997-2002 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Sophomore Leadership Program Interfraternity Council, 1997-2003 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Rush Interfraternity Council, 1997-2004 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Elections GPAs Interfraternity Council, 1997-2005 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Interfraternity Council, 1997-2006 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: "+/- Talking Points", 1997-2007 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Unfoldered 43, 1997-2008 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Risk Management, 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Housing, 1996-1999 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Faculty Advisors, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Sophomore Leadership Program, 1996-2001 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Sophomore Leadership Program, 1996-2002 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Rush, 1996-2003 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Unfoldered 44, 1995-1997 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: IFC, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: GPA List, Interfraternity Council President's List, Elections, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Interfraternity Council, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Untitled V: Unfoldered 45, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Untitled V: Untitled 10, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Untitled V: Meetings with VPG, Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Interfraternity Council, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Archives: Unfoldered 46, 1992-2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Archives: Constitutions, Past and Present, 1974-circa 2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Archives: Unfoldered 47, 1964-1998 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Interfraternity Council Folders: Greek Life, 1979-1995 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Pledge Educator: Unfoldered 48, 2000-2008 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Pledge Educator: Recruitment/New Member Progs., 2001-2007 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Pledge Educator: Pledge Trainer Meeting, 1999-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Pledge Educator: Pledge Educator Meeting, 2001-2003 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Pledge Educator: Pledge Educator Meetings, 2001-2003 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Untitled 11, 2006-2007 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Letter to FY male parents, 2003-2005 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Chapter Advisors, 2001-2003 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Recruitment Chair Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Executive Board, 2003-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 49, 2003-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Expansion Committee, 1995-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Example Expansion Procedures, 2003-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 50, 2002-2003 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Executive Board, 2002-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Recruitment Discussion, 2002-2005 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Elections, 2002-2006 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 51, 2002-2007 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: SE Interfraternity Council, Atlanta, Georgia, 2002-2003 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 52, 2001-2002 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Retreat, 2001-2002 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Rush Orientation, 1997-2002 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Recruitment, 2000-2002 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 53, 2001-2002 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 54, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Duke Interfraternity Council, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Chris Dieterich, IFC President, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Recruitment, Spring, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 55, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 56, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Alcohol Policy, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Elections GPAs, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Rush, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Faculty Advisors, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Risk Management, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Sophomore Leadership Program, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Delta Chi, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Fraternity Issues, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Untitled W: Unfoldered 57, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Untitled W: Greek Leadership Course, circa 2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Interfraternity Council, circa 2000 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Unfoldered 58, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Risk Management, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Alcohol Policy, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Recognition Guidelines, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Rush, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Folders Interfraternity Council: Sophomore Leadership Program, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Files: Interfraternity Council: Elections GPAs, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled 12, 2002-2004 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Files: Men's Recruitment, 2004-2005 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled X: Unfoldered 59, 2001-2005 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled X: Rush Surveys, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled X: Unfoldered 60, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Y: Interfraternity Council Recruitment, Chapter Bid Lists, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Y: Interfraternity Council Recruitment, 2nd Round Invite Lists, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Y: Interfraternity Council Recruitment, 1st Round Invite Lists, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Y: Unfoldered 61, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Unfoldered 62, circa 1996 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Pledge Educator Forms, Spring, 2005 February-March (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Zody Interfraternity Council Bios, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Interfraternity Council Recruitment: 1st Round Invitation Lists, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Interfraternity Council Recruitment: 2nd Round Invitation Lists, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Interfraternity Council Recruitment: Chapter Bid Lists, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Interfraternity Council Recruitment: 2nd Round Invitations, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled Z: Interfraternity Council Recruitment: 1st Round Invitation Lists, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Interfraternity Council Recruitment: Surveys, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Rush: Dry Rush Information, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled AA: Duke Delta Kappa Local Pledge Manual, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled AA: Unfoldered 63, 2004-2005 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled AB: Unfoldered 64, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled AB: Pledge Manuals, 2000-2004 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled AB: Unfoldered 65, circa 2003 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Untitled 13, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Historical Reference, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Clarybel Files: Alcohol, 1986-1996 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AC: Unfoldered 66, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AC: Greek Life Task Force, 1994 March-April (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AC: Unfoldered 67, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Unfoldered 68, 1999 October-November (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Advisory Board, 1999 April-November (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Faculty, 1997-1999 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Members, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Alcohol, 1997-1998 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Members, 1997-1998 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Elections/GPAs/Alcohol Policy, 1996-1997 (Box 11)